paydif.com 2015-11-03

# Privacy policy | PayDif - online payments made easy

All our information is gathered and compiled various ways. This information includes your personal information, including addresses, phone numbers and credit card details. We gathered this information through emails sent to us, sites and pages used by you, registered sites and surveys you filled in. PayDif protects your details including your credit card information which is protected according to Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI-DSS). It should be noted that some data will be used in the provision of our services. We do not disclose, share or sell your personal information without your consent and on paper, except in circumstances such as:

– Investigating, preventing or taking action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the terms of use of PayDif, or as required by law.  
– When we employ another company to perform tasks for us, they may need to share your information with the company to be able to provide you the product or service you want.  
– When ordering products or services or when we have your absolute permission.  
– If our company is acquired or merged with another company. If this happens, and before we transfer your personal details, you will be notified or it will be posted on our website as they will be subject to a different privacy policy.  
Please note that we reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If changes are made you will be notified through our website.

### Utility and Functions of your personal data

We consider all personal data, any information that identifies or could be used to identify, locate or even contact a certain person. All information collected is for the purpose of billing, shipping of products / services, identification and authentication, contact, improving services and research. All data and information collected is subject to the Privacy Policy.  
By registering for PayDif, we ask for your personal details, your name, company´s name, email address, billing information and your credit card information. Clients that have free accounts do not have to enter their credit card information, unless, of course, they want to activate their account.

As our client, you enter the buying and selling process of our service, automatically you agree to our Privacy Policy. As you agree, all personal data from other users and customers, through the PayDif service, is used only for communications related to our service and are not unsolicited commercial messages. You are not allowed to add someone who has been your customer / buyer, to your e-mail list nor to your physical mail, without their formal consent. We do not tolerate spam or any threat messages. 

### Security

To demonstrate the importance of your personal data, especially sensitive data like credit card information, this information is encrypted with AES-256 encryption, using the method of technology, Secure Socket Layer (SSL). As service-level PCI DSS provider, we follow all requirements of PCI-DSS and implement additional industry standards generally accepted to protect personal information received during the reception and after.There is no method of receiving, transmitting or storing information via Internet that is 100% secure, so even using commercial accord means to protect your data, we can not guarantee its absolute security. Any questions about security please email support@PayDif.com.

### Disclosure

PayDif may disclose personal information in special circumstances, such as to comply with court orders requiring us to do so, or when you violate the Terms and Conditions of our service.  
PayDif may use third party services to provide your services and we may share personal information with these providers. We demand that any company with whom we share personal information, to protect data with our policy and limit the use of such personal information to perform services for PayDif.  
PayDif does not sell or provide personal data to other companies for marketing or other services for their own products or services.

### Our Clients Data Storage

PayDif owns the data storage, databases and all rights to the application, however, PayDif makes no obligation to the rights over your personal data. You retain all rights to your data and we will never contact your clients directly, or use your information for the benefit of our own business or to compete with you in any way.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which includes an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and are stored on your hard drive. A different cookie is assigned to each computer that enters our website. These cookies help us identify you electronically and give us an opportunity to show relevant ads on our website.

### Google Analytics and Remarketing

PayDif uses a service provided by Google, called Google Analytics (GA). Google Analytics allows us to reach people who have visited our site, showing them relevant ads when they visit other websites in the Google Display Network. This is called “Remarketing”.  
As stated above, cookies can be used to track your session on our website which gives us the opportunity to show relevant ads, costumed by Google and other suppliers, on our website. In other words, when you visit our website you can view advertisements posted by Google or third parties.  
Through cookies, third parties can collect your information while you are visiting our website or while you are on other websites too. Based on your previous visits in various places on the Internet, these third parties may use your information to show ads, not only on our website but on any other site as well. We do not control the content of the ads that appear on your display.  
Using our website without opting out, means that you understand and agree to data collection to provide you with ads, using Google Analytics, and third-party cookies based on your previous visits to our website and other places on the Internet.

### PCI-DSS

To protect our customers and keep your PayDif account secure, we use the same safety industry standard of large credit card companies. Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS) is a set of security requirements directed by PCI “Security Standards Council,” a combined effort by the payment brands, including Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the safe handling of credit information from merchants and service providers.

### Concerns or Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be emailed to support@paydif.com or by mail to:

PayDif, lda  
Rua das Feiteirinhas A, 7D  
9200-038 Caniçal  
Portugal
